Division of Vertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Collecting Permits, Series VII
  - New Jersey. Past New Jersey collecting permits., 001030
  - New Mexico. Past New Mexico collecting permits., 001031
  - New York. Past New York collecting permits., 001032
  - North Carolina. Past North Carolina collecting permits., 001033
  - North Dakota. Past North Dakota collecting permits., 001034
  - Ohio. Past Ohio collecting permits., 001035
  - Oklahoma. Past Oklahoma collecting permits., 001036
  - Pennsylvania. Past Pennsylvania collecting permits., 001037
  - Puerto Rico. Past Puerto Rico collecting permits., 001038
  - South Carolina. Past South Carolina collecting permits., 001039
  - Tennesse. Past Tennessee collecting permits., 001040
  - Texas. Past Texas collecting permits., 001041
  - USDA Permit. Information on the USDA permit., 001372
  - Vermont. Past Vermont collecting permits., 001042
  - Virginia. Past Virginia collecting permits., 001043
  - West Virginia. Past West Virginia collecting permits., 001044
  - Wisconsin. Past Wisconsin collecting permits., 001045
- Eggshell Micrographs, Series VIII
  - Accipitridae. Golden Eagle, Red-Shouldered Hawk., 001077
  - Aepyornithidae., 001054
  - Alcidae. Thick-billed Murre., 001100
  - Anatidae., 001074
  - Anhimidae., 001073
  - Anhingidae., 001066
  - Apterygidae. Kiwi., 001053
  - Aramidae. Limpkin., 001088
  - Ardeidae., 001068
  - Black Swan. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001135
  - Black Swan. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001136
  - Bucerotidae. Hornbill., 001111
  - Burhinidae. Burhinus oidochemus., 001094
  - Calcite. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001140
  - Calcite. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001141
  - Calcite. Na Sulfide. 30 min boil., 001142
  - Calcite. EDTA. 30 min., 001143
  - Capitonidae. Barbet., 001112
  - Casariidae., 001050
  - Cathartidae., 001075
  - Ciconiidae., 001071
  - Clorox., 001152
  - Cochleariidae., 001069
  - Columbidae. Band-tailed Pigeon., 001102
  - Coraciidae. Roller., 001109
  - Cracidae., 001081
  - Cuculidae. Black-billed Cuckoo., 001104
  - Dinornithidae. Moa., 001052
  - Diomedeidae. Yellow billed albatross., 001058
  - Dromiceidae. Emu., 001051
  - Eagle. NaOH., 001132
  - Eggshell Special., 001157
  - Emu. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001120
  - Emu. NaOH. 10 min boil., 001121
  - Emu. NaOH. 20 min boil., 001122
  - Emu. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001123
  - Emu. NaOH. 16 hrs., 001124
  - Emu. Na Sulfide. 30 min boil., 001125
  - Emu. HCl., 001126
  - Emu. EDTA. 1 min., 001127
  - Emu. EDTA. 5 & 10 min., 001128
  - Emu. EDTA. 20 min., 001129
  - Emu. EDTA. 60 min., 001130
  - Emu. EDTA. 4 days., 001131
  - Eurylaimidae. Psarisomus dalhousiae., 001114
  - Falconidae., 001079
  - Fregatidae., 001067
  - Fringeillidae., 001116
  - Gavidae., 001056
  - Glareolidae. Glareola pratinicola., 001095
  - Gruidae. Sandhill Crane., 001087
  - Haematopodidae. Oystercatcher., 001092
  - Hydrobatidae., 001060
  - Icteridae. Cowbird., 001115
  - Incinerated., 001133
  - Jacana spinosa. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001134
  - Jacanidae. Jacana spinosa., 001090
  - King Penguin. HCl., 001138
  - Laridae. Franklin's Gull., 001098
  - Laridae. Gull-billed Tern, Frankin's Gull., 001113
  - Megapodidae., 001080
  - Meleagrididae., 001085
  - Miscellaneous., 001158
  - Numididae. Guinea Fowl., 001084
  - Pandionidae., 001078
  - Pelecanoididae., 001061
  - Pelicanidae., 001063
  - Phaethontidae., 001062
  - Phalacrocoraidae., 001065
  - Phalaropodidae. Wilson's Phalarope., 001093
  - Phasianidae. Chicken, Bobwhite Quail., 001083
  - Podargidae. Podargus strigoides., 001107
  - Podicepedidae., 001057
  - Pore Casts., 001117
  - Procellariidae., 001059
  - Psittacidae. Brown-throated Parakeet., 001103
  - Pterochidae., 001101
  - Rallidae. Purple Gallinule., 001089
  - Red-Winged Black Bird. Not incubated., 001118
  - Red-Winged Black Bird. Incubated., 001119
  - Red-Winged Black Bird. Not incubated. NaOH. 30 min boil., 001139
  - Rheidae., 001049
  - Rostratulidae. Painted Snipe., 001091
  - Rynchopidae. Black Skimmer., 001099
  - Sagittariidae., 001076
  - Scopidae., 001070
  - Spheniscidae., 001047
  - Stercorariidae. Longtailed Jaeger., 001097
  - Strigidae. Barred Owl., 001106
  - Struthionidae., 001048
  - Sulidae., 001064
  - Swan. HCl., 001137
  - Tetraonidae., 001082
  - Thinocoridae. Thinocrous rumicivorus., 001096
  - Threskiornithidae., 001072
  - Tinamidae., 001055
  - Trochilidae. Rufous Hummingbird., 001108
  - Turnicidae., 001086
  - Tytonidae. Common Barn Owl., 001105
  - Upupidae. Hoopoe., 001110
  - White Pelican. before EDTA., 001144
  - White Pelican. HCl. 10 seconds., 001145
  - White Pelican. EDTA. 30 min., 001146
  - White Pelican. EDTA. 60 min., 001147
  - White Pelican. EDTA. 1.5 hrs., 001148
  - White Pelican. EDTA. 16 hrs., 001149
  - White Pelican. EDTA. 5 days., 001150
  - White Pelican. Broken after EDTA. 5 days., 001151
  - White Pelican. Clorox 16 hrs. EDTA 30 min., 001153
  - White Pelican. Clorox 16 hrs. EDTA 2 hrs., 001154
  - White Pelican. Clorox 16 hrs. EDTA 16 hrs., 001155
  - White Pelican. EDTA 30 min. Clorox 16 hrs., 001156
- Fish Data Sheets, Series IX
  Fish and Amphibian data sheets orginized by collecting event, collector, or location. Mostly fish data with some amphibian by-catch data.
  - Alabama., 001178
  - Alaska., 001179
  - Antarctica., 2004; 001166
  - Antarctica., 2006; 001167
  - Antarctica., 2008; 001168
  - Antarctica., 2009; 001169
  - Antarctica., 2010; 001170
  - Arkansas., 001180
  - Bear Seamount., 001176
  - Connecticut., 001181
  - Curacao., 2010; 001212
  - Curacao., 001171
  - D. Skelly MANCH Sites., 001209
  - D. Skelly Sites., 2001; 001174
  - D. Skelly TOLL Sites., 001210
  - D. Skelly YM Sites., 001211
  - Europe., 001175
  - Florida., 001182
  - GWC Fish., 001160
  - Georgia., 001183
  - Gunter Blennies., 001207
  - Hera., 2007; 001208
  - Ice Fish., 2001; 001164
  - Ice Fish., 2003; 001162
  - Ice Fish., 2004; 001163
  - Ice Fish., 2006; 001165
  - Illinois., 001185
  - Indiana., 001186
  - KLH Sites., 001161
  - Kentucky., 001187
  - Maine., 001188
  - Maryland., 001189
  - Massachusetts., 001190
  - Minnesota., 001191
  - Miscellaneous., 001184
  - Mississippi., 001192
  - Missouri., 001193
  - Mixed Localities., 001173
  - NOAA., 001177
  - New Jersey., 001194
  - New York., 001195
  - No Data., 001172
  - No Locality Information., 001196
  - North Carolina., 001197
  - Ohio., 001198
  - Oklahoma., 001199
  - Pennsylvania., 001200
  - RV PISCES., 2012; 001213
  - Rhode Island., 001201
  - Tennessee., 001202
  - Texas., 001203
  - Vermont., 001204
  - Virginia., 001205
  - West Virginia., 001206
- Miscellaneous, Series X
  - AMNH specimens to check., 001369
  - Accession Ledgers. Copies of Peabody Accession Ledgers No. 1-9., 001427
  - Animal Dealers. List of Animal dealers., 1966-1967; 001343
  - Animal Dealers. Mostly mammals., 001365
  - Archived Calendars., 001410
  - Audubon Copper Plates., 001443
    - American Scoter Duck. Copper plate engraving of Black Scoter (Melanitta americana) corresponding to Plate CCCCVIII (408) No. 82 in John James Audubon?s "Birds of America" double elephant folio., 001445
    - Black Skimmer or Shearwater. Copper plate engraving of Black Skimmer (Rynchops niger) corresponding to Plate CCCXXIII (323) No. 65 in John James Audubon?s "Birds of America" double elephant folio., 001444
    - Black Vulture or Carrion Crow. Copper plate engraving of two Black Vultures (Coragyps atratus) feeding on a White-tailed Deer carcass. It corresponds to Plate CVI (106) No. 22 in John James Audubon?s "Birds of America" double elephant folio., 001446
    - Herring Gull. Copper plate engraving of American Herring Gull (Larus smithsonianus) corresponding to Plate CCXCI (291) No. 59 in John James Audubon?s "Birds of America" double elephant folio., 001447
    - Marsh Hawk. Copper plate engraving of Northern Harrier (Circus hudsonius) corresponding to Plate CCCLVI (356) No. 72 in John James Audubon?s "Birds of America" double elephant folio., 001448
  - Bird Preservation - Fluid. Information on fluid preservation of birds., 001342
  - Bird Shipments., 001349
  - Birds Lacking from Collection. A list of bird species not represented in the skins collection., 001347
  - Block Island Banding., 001408
  - Borrowed Specimens., 001389
  - Bruce Museum Bird Lables. Copies of Bruce Museum Bird Labels., 001439
  - Bug Room Specimens., 001398
  - CITES. CITES information., 001434
  - Canary Hybrid., 001337
  - Carriker Exchanges. Correspondence, lists etc., 001436
  - Collection Information., 001346
  - Cornell University NSF Proposal. Requested by Fred Sibley to review., 001361
  - DEP Mammal Donations., 001397
  - Data Slips. Data slips for mounted specimens., 001429
  - Deed of Gift. Copy of deed of gift form. See YPM Acc.11017., 001373
  - Dog Skins. List of dogs skins., 001390
  - Egg Blowing Tool., 001441
  - Egg Collection Exchanges. Egg Collection Exchanges., 001336
  - Eutamias. Eutamias inventory., 001338
  - Field Museum Loan. Information about missing specimens from the loan., 1966; 001350
  - Gargantua., 001396
  - Horse Island Bird Banding. Michael Anderson & Celia Lewis., 001404
  - Horse Island Bird Sightings., 1990-1993; 001407
  - Horse Island Bird Sightings., 1994; 001405
  - Horse Island Bird Sightings., 1995-1996; 001406
  - Information Requests., 001358
  - Inventory. Inventory of old Bird Room., 001345
  - KBT - Peregrines., 001399
  - Lane Case Purchase., 001359
  - Mammal Collection. Miscellaneous correspondence related to mammal collection., 001438
  - Mammal Exchange?., 001354
  - Mammal Labels. Miscellaneous stray mammal labels., 001220
  - Mammal Labels., 001395
  - Mammal Publications., 001402
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence., 001360
  - Miscellaneous label., 001355
  - Miscellaneous., 001340
  - Miscellaneous., 001348
  - Miscellaneous., 001363
  - Nighthawk Slides. 35mm slides of Nighthawks nesting on the roof., 001327
  - Office of Naval Research. Progress reports, correspondence, etc. relating to research done by the Bingham Oceanographic Collection., 001442
  - Osborn Cabinet Inventory. Inventory of C.L. Remingtons Osborn Cabinets., 001440
  - Osteology Specimens., 001437
  - Postilla. List of fluid preserved specimens published in Postilla., 001364
  - Preperation Techniques., 001366
  - Proctor - Avian Anatomy. Handouts., 001401
  - Reindeer Collection., 001394
  - Revised Checklist of Nebraska Birds. Fred Sibley copy of Revised Checklist of Nebraska Birds., 1958; 001344
  - Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Circus Specimens. Correspondence related to YPm Acc. 3779., 001392
  - Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Circus: Old Bill. Correspondence related to YPm Acc. 3780., 001393
  - Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Circus. Archives related to YPM Acc. 4920., 001400
  - Scanned Ledgers. List of Kirtas'd ledgers., 001403
  - Skins to be tanned., 001367
  - Species Index. List of genera and species lacking in the Peabody Collection., 001435
  - Specimens sent to bug room., 001368
  - Tufted Duck., 001341
  - Turtox Quiz sheets and anwer keys., 001370
  - Uncataloged Collections., 001371
  - Unidentified Mammal Specimens. List of unidentified mammals., 1980; 001356
  - West Campus Monkeys. List of alcohol prepped monkey specimens., 001391
- Card Catalogs, Series XI
  - Ichtyology Card Catalog. Gray Museum fish collection card catalog., 001330
  - Mammology Card Catalog. Osteology mammal card catalog, in numeric order., 001331
  - Mammology Card Catalog. Osteology mammal card catalog, odered by Family., 001332
  - Ornithology Card Catalog. Alcohol and osteo prepped specimens only. 5 boxes. Includes an evelope with a key to the collector abbreviations., 001329
  - Ornithology Card Catalog. Osteology prepped bird card catalog, ordered numerically. In 2 boxes., 001333
  - Ornithology Card Catalog. Skin prepped specimens, mostly Bird, some mammal. 2 boxes., 001424
  - Ornithology Card Catalog. A Series. 2 boxes. Stanley Ball Series., 001425
- Mammal Research, Series XII
  Notes on mammal research.
  - Carlito., 001375
  - Cheirogaleus., 001377
  - Eulemur., 001378
  - Galago., 001379
  - Galagoides., 001380
  - Hapalemur., 001381
  - Loris., 001382
  - Microcebus., 001383
  - Mirza., 001384
  - Miscellaneous Lemur., 001374
  - Nycticebus., 001385
  - Otolemur., 001386
  - Perodicticus., 001387
  - Varecia., 001388
- Visitor Information, Series XIII
  - Visitors., 2001-2002; 001411
  - Visitors., 2002-2003; 001412
  - Visitors., 2003-2004; 001413
  - Visitors., 2004-2005; 001414
  - Visitors., 2005-2006; 001415
  - Visitors., 2006-2007; 001416
  - Visitors., 2007-2008; 001417
  - Visitors., 2008-2009; 001418
  - Visitors., 2009-2010; 001419
  - Visitors., 2010-2011; 001420
  - Visitors., 2011-2012; 001421
  - Visitors., 2012-2013; 001422
  - Visitors. Ornithology & Mammology Visitors., 2013-2014; 001423
- Exhibits, Series XIV
  - Bird Hall Tags. Tags for specimens in the Bird Hall., 001431